ok let's get started so the theme of
好吧，让我们开始这样 的主题
本周谈论优化
ok let's get started so the theme of
this week is talking about optimizing
我们创建的汇编输出也可以
采取我们所拥有的这些计划
this week is talking about optimizing
the assembly output we create so can we
输入并在前往结果的路上
装配我们可以做智能事情
the assembly output we create so can we
take these programs that we have as
避免产生这么多
说明或我们可以生成更聪明的
take these programs that we have as
input and on their way to the resulting
指令使用更少的内存所有这些
各种各样的事情 ，今天我 想
input and on their way to the resulting
assembly can we do intelligent things to
谈谈有三种想法
三个不同的 想法落入
assembly can we do intelligent things to
avoid either generating so many
三种不同类别 的编译器
优化有三种
avoid either generating so many
instructions or can we generate smarter
表面上的小想法，如果你
我想投入大量详细的工作
instructions or can we generate smarter
instructions use less memory all these
或写GCC团队想要投入
你可以看到多年的详细工作
instructions use less memory all these
kinds of things and so today I want to
轨迹跨越你的方式
越来越多的精力投入到这件事情
kinds of things and so today I want to
talk about three ideas there's sort of
在 131我们 真的很好
没有成千上万的男人
talk about three ideas there's sort of
three different ideas that fall into
和女人的时间 投入 我们的
编译器是什么进入了
three different ideas that fall into
three different categories of compiler
像GCC 这样的编译器有很多
思考许多不同的案例
three different categories of compiler
optimization there are three sort of
所以我们要谈谈 一些
今天 几个 有趣的案例
optimization there are three sort of
little ideas on the surface that if you
不同 种类的编译器
我们可能尝试优化，这些是
little ideas on the surface that if you
wanted to put in lots of detailed work
其实类似的事情 ，
海湾合作委员会只做了第一件事
wanted to put in lots of detailed work
or write the GCC team wanted to put in
我们要谈论 的 实际
前两 件事是GCC的事情
or write the GCC team wanted to put in
years of detailed work you can see a
特别是我所拥有的
屏幕在这里是在左侧我
years of detailed work you can see a
trajectory spanning out of how you'd put
刚刚复制了我们的代码
参考实现 ii-if from
trajectory spanning out of how you'd put
more and more effort into this thing to
像眼镜蛇和 响尾蛇 ， 它的
如果需要做的话，做什么编译
more and more effort into this thing to
make things really really good in 131 we
这里调用 的条件 表达式
如果exper检查它是否是布尔值
make things really really good in 131 we
don't have hundreds of thousands of men
因为在我们的
我们的语言我们关心 这些
don't have hundreds of thousands of men
and women hours to put into our
欺负ins 然后它有代码
当时的分支， 该代码
and women hours to put into our
compilers that's what goes into a
else分支，它检查 真实性
我 的 右手 也是如此
compilers that's what goes into a
compiler like GCC it has lots of
方是一个更详细的模式匹配
e如果那时在左侧 a
compiler like GCC it has lots of
thinking about many many different cases
更详细的模式匹配比什么
在左手边这么 左手
thinking about many many different cases
so we're going to talk about some
边匹配将匹配看起来的程序
就像X，然后一些II 1 LC 2他们会
so we're going to talk about some
interesting cases today across a few
匹配看起来像某些东西的东西
函数调用某个值 所以匹配任何 值
interesting cases today across a few
different kinds of compiler
如果表达 我们可以
写一个 你写的表达式if if
different kinds of compiler
optimizations we might try and these are
你解析它把它变成抽象的
语法并将其与该案例进行匹配
optimizations we might try and these are
actually quite similar to things that
它会匹配，这就是编译
对于它， 只有 右手边的情况
actually quite similar to things that
GCC does but one of the first things
如果表达式看起来匹配
喜欢 这里 的 名字 保持 不变
GCC does but one of the first things
we're going to talk about actually the
一些表达， 然后在其他
拥有它只会 匹配
we're going to talk about actually the
first two things are things that GCC
事情呐喊 更大而不是更少
只会去匹配的地方
first two things are things that GCC
does in particular so what I have on the
条件位置的东西有一个
大于第一个问题可以吗？
does in particular so what I have on the
screen here is on the left-hand side I
谈谈我们可能会有什么
如果我们知道的话，可以做得更好
screen here is on the left-hand side I
just copied the code that we have in our
如果我们知道的话，与这种情况相匹
我们只是匹配ifs
just copied the code that we have in our
reference implementation for ii-if from
这种情况我们有一个大于
我们能做些什么才能做得更好
reference implementation for ii-if from
like cobra and Diamondback and it's
那会更聪明
我们正在生成的指令
like cobra and Diamondback and it's
doing what if needs to do it compiles
所有通用案例都是这样的
只需30秒 左右我们能做 什么
doing what if needs to do it compiles
the conditional expression here called
那样做会更聪明
右侧
the conditional expression here called
if exper checks if it's a boolean
有没有讲谈 了谈
关于它谈谈谈话
if exper checks if it's a boolean
because in our
好的想法有一些不同的 想法
在这个空间，但如果我们有想法的想法
because in our
our language we care about these being
这些额外的信息我们可以做些什么
做的更好什么 有一些想法， 我看
our language we care about these being
bully ins and then it has the code for
点头的想法，如果哦所以你说是否
我们对1和2有所了解
bully ins and then it has the code for
the then branch and the code for the
让我们想象一下 让我们得到 更多
具体你说 另一个
the then branch and the code for the
else branch and it checks for trueness
想法所以我只是 要去把虚线
这里，所以我们知道我们在谈论
else branch and it checks for trueness
too so what I have on the right-hand
更具体的东西 但如果我们想要的话
谈 事情，其中一个或多个
too so what I have on the right-hand
side is a more detailed pattern match on
在这种情况下，这些是数字
在这种情况下，我们可以说我们很好
side is a more detailed pattern match on
e if then is on the left-hand side a
绝对只需要说明
对于else 分支，因为这是
e if then is on the left-hand side a
more detailed pattern match than what's
总是要评价 为假
这就是你正确得到的
more detailed pattern match than what's
on the left-hand side so this left hand
如果我们知道的话更加正确
我可以进行更详细的比赛
on the left-hand side so this left hand
side match will match programs that look
写在哪里而不是有一个e1和
e2在这里我可以写出 类似的东西
side match will match programs that look
like if X then some II 1 LC 2 they'll
如果这两个数字都正确怎么办？
这是一个 想法，我们 很酷
like if X then some II 1 LC 2 they'll
match things that look like if some
可能会使用实际上 会使用这个想法
与后来 在后面的
match things that look like if some
function call on some value so match any
但是如果 我们不知道怎么办呢
E还有更多的东西 -
function call on some value so match any
possible if expression that we could
耶可以节省一个布尔检查 ÿ 请
我们可以保存一个布尔检查， 也许我们
possible if expression that we could
write an e if expression you write if
可以保存布尔检查其他想法
什么也可以节省一个
write an e if expression you write if
you parse it turn it into the abstract
分支也可能保存分支
保存布尔检查保存的想法
you parse it turn it into the abstract
syntax and match it against that case
分支我们会回到其他人那里
想法其他想法
syntax and match it against that case
it'll match and that's what will compile
好吧，我会回来说为什么可以
我们跳过 布尔检查为什么会这样
it'll match and that's what will compile
for it this right hand case is only
好的 ，如果有 错误 的话会怎样
如果您想要 导致错误怎么办？
for it this right hand case is only
going to match if expressions that look
那么我怎么知道啊所以大于
II 1或e 2产生错误或
going to match if expressions that look
like keep the names the same here with
他们的非数字大于
产生错误，在这种情况下
like keep the names the same here with
some expression and then in else
程序完成后我们不用 担心
关于这个子表达的答案
some expression and then in else
possession it's only going to match
因为我们得到了一个错误 ，这个
在许多语言中都是如此
possession it's only going to match
things whoops a greater not less it's
Java 你不再担心了
回答这个子表达式和一个if
things whoops a greater not less it's
only going to match things where the
如果抛出一些异常
异常处理程序会处理你
only going to match things where the
thing in conditional position has a
不必担心本地
这里大于总是返回一个
thing in conditional position has a
greater than sign first question can you
布尔总是把一个布尔值在EAX 作为
只要它成功， 我们不必
greater than sign first question can you
talk about what might be something we
担心失败的情况因为
我们在这里生成的代码不是
talk about what might be something we
could do better if we knew we were
代码不是代码
处理错误所以我们 知道，因为我们知道
could do better if we knew we were
matching against this case if we knew
那个结果 必须更大
一个 布尔值 ，我们不需要这个整个测试
matching against this case if we knew
that we were only matching ifs against
bool chunk 这部分插入
测试池的代码以及我们添加它的位置
that we were only matching ifs against
this case where we had a greater than
在这里的列表中
这些不需要成为其中的一部分
this case where we had a greater than
what could we do better what could we do
比赛
如果我们只是 考虑 移动
what could we do better what could we do
that would be smarter than the
代码结束 并实现它
在这里匹配案例现在 我们还在
that would be smarter than the
instructions we're generating for if in
要去必须做一些东西 ， 有
用if和 then 和else做
instructions we're generating for if in
all the generic cases like what this
以及那些编译它们的东西
子表达式，但我们不需要
all the generic cases like what this
just for 30 seconds or so what could we
测试池你 建议我们
可以摆脱一个分支机构 是一个
just for 30 seconds or so what could we
do that would be smarter on the
从中间的建议是 什么
分支案例， 你建议我们可以
do that would be smarter on the
right-hand side
摆脱，如果我们实施大于
有分支哦，所以你说 我们喜欢
there's no talking talk about it talk
里面大于操作那里
可能是那里的一个分支，我们可以
there's no talking talk about it talk
about it talk about it talk talk
让那个分支改为做if事
所以也许我们可以弄巧 用
okay ideas there's a few different ideas
编译大于此类
与if同时如此
okay ideas there's a few different ideas
in this space but ideas ideas if we have
那里有一些机会没关系
所以也许我们可以深入研究
in this space but ideas ideas if we have
this extra information what can we maybe
探索那个选项 的重点我
当我提出这个问题时，请记住
this extra information what can we maybe
do better what are some ideas I see
有趣的想法我没有这个想法
当我选择这个例子的时候
do better what are some ideas I see
nodding idea if oh so you're saying if
我挑选的时候我 想到的主要事情
这个例子指出了这个bool
nodding idea if oh so you're saying if
we know something about a 1 and a 2 so
我们可以摆脱这个布尔值的情况
凭借我们知道的事实来检查
we know something about a 1 and a 2 so
let's imagine let's get even more
如果我们在 if中 做得更好
它会有条件的位置
let's imagine let's get even more
specific right you're saying another
产生一个布尔值，所以没有必要
检查没有办法省略这个
specific right you're saying another
idea so I'm just gonna put a dotted line
代码可能导致该程序有一个
不同的答案或有错误的时候
idea so I'm just gonna put a dotted line
here so we know that we're talking about
它 之前没有错误
会有相同的答案，所以
here so we know that we're talking about
something more specific but if we wanted
非常有趣它意味着我们
可以写出这些更详细的比赛
something more specific but if we wanted
to talk about things where one or more
关于当前一些表达的案例
编译器，我们有这个特别
to talk about things where one or more
of these was numbers then in this case
在执行这些标记的表达式中很有用
检查错误， 但还有其他 错误
of these was numbers then in this case
in this case we could say well we're
情况下，这可能是 有用的 ，以及
我们可以写出这些更详细的匹配
in this case we could say well we're
definitely just need the instructions
病例和选择做一个更好的工作
我们为a生成的指令
definitely just need the instructions
for the else branch because this is
给出表达所以这个网站这个想法
有一个名字，我只是要把它写下来
for the else branch because this is
always gonna evaluate to false right
在这里， 这个 想法 很好
真的 - 这是 一个庞大的 家庭
always gonna evaluate to false right
that's what you're getting at right
这里 的 技术， 但总体思路是
称为指令选择，这是
that's what you're getting at right
right so if we knew even more right
现在就明白这个想法
我们为每个人写了一个案例
right so if we knew even more right
there's a more detailed match I could
用我们的语言表达右EF
有与 它 匹配 的 一个案例
there's a more detailed match I could
write where instead of having a e1 and
编译器EBU欺负数量 应用程序的一切
有一个案例匹配 它
write where instead of having a e1 and
e2 here I could write something like
编译器，只有一个 选项
我们为每个人生成哪些指令
e2 here I could write something like
what if these are both numbers right
表达我们生成它和想法
如果我们 ，教学选择很好
what if these are both numbers right
that's an idea it's a cool idea that we
有关正在发生的 事情的 更多信息
在表达式上我们可以 做一些
that's an idea it's a cool idea that we
might use actually gonna use the idea
我们生成代码时更聪明的事情
省略省略这样的检查是
might use actually gonna use the idea
related to that later in a later in the
一个想法， 所以我想谈谈这个
更普遍的，但之前我说说
related to that later in a later in the
lecture but what about if we don't know
更普遍的是我想提几个
这里的例子是另一套
lecture but what about if we don't know
anything more still about a 1 in E -
这里的示例是嵌套匹配
加上他们需要一些信件
anything more still about a 1 in E -
yeah can save a boolean check Y please
我要问 的问题 是
这些
yeah can save a boolean check Y please
can we save a boolean check ok maybe we
其中哪些不会让我们跳过标签
检查正确，所以我们只是看到了如果我们
can we save a boolean check ok maybe we
can save a boolean check other ideas
知道 有条件的东西
在if中的位置比我们大
can save a boolean check other ideas
what's that also potentially save a
可以跳过 标签检查 布尔值
它有什么关于这个所以 这些 在这里的四
what's that also potentially save a
branch also potentially save a branch so
嵌套嵌套二进制文件的选项
运营商
branch also potentially save a branch so
ideas of saving boolean check saving a
好吧，让我们这样做应该说得好
这应该说EEPROM 约对不起
ideas of saving boolean check saving a
branch we'll come back to those other
那只是为了那种方式的一致性
五四三二一
branch we'll come back to those other
ideas other ideas
好吧， 有 一种奇怪的感觉
这些选项所以我想让你 谈谈
okay I'm gonna come back and say why can
关于它只是 20 或 30秒
简单地谈谈它
okay I'm gonna come back and say why can
we skip the boolean check why is that
好吧那么首先是什么呢
这里 或者 至少 是什么 答案
we skip the boolean check why is that
okay yeah what if there's like an error
就像 这里 最明显的 答案一样
好吧在 B和C 我们正在做一个加号 和
okay yeah what if there's like an error
what if you wanna need to cause an error
那么我们知道 第 一个论点是
无论是数字还是其他加上 我们
what if you wanna need to cause an error
then how do I know yeah so greater than
知道数字不好
需要检查数字和
then how do I know yeah so greater than
either II 1 or e 2 produces an error or
我们知道plus plus表达式
我们可以在B和C中返回数字
either II 1 or e 2 produces an error or
their non numbers so greater than
绝对省略标签检查
第一个参数我们没有检查
their non numbers so greater than
produces an error in which case the
这个表达式的标签或者这个
表达我们 可以跳过它，也许
produces an error in which case the
program's done we don't need to worry
甚至产生 更加智能
在第一种情况下的说明
program's done we don't need to worry
about the answer for this sub expression
如果我们有一个功能，请回答
申请我们不知道那么多
about the answer for this sub expression
because we got an error right and this
本地到这个模式 匹配 什么
可能会从那里归还
because we got an error right and this
would be true in many languages right in
以我们编译器的方式运行
设置我们根本不知道 多少
would be true in many languages right in
Java you would no longer worry about the
函数的返回值 直到我们
称他们为选项 A这 真的很难
Java you would no longer worry about the
answer for this sub expression and an if
看看我们如何跳过支票检查
通过 使用选项我们必须 做
answer for this sub expression and an if
if an exception was thrown some
函数调用看看 回来了什么
然后做加法与它 使
if an exception was thrown some
exception handlers gonna handle that you
这里最明显的答案 是a和 它
一些预期的答案， 但D是
exception handlers gonna handle that you
don't have to worry about it locally
故意怪异的B是故意的
很奇怪D的奇怪之处是什么
don't have to worry about it locally
here so greater than always returns a
关于D是的是的，是 的， 是的
肯定会产生一个布尔值
here so greater than always returns a
boolean always puts a boolean in EAX as
意味着加号表达肯定
在运行时会导致错误
boolean always puts a boolean in EAX as
long as it succeeds and we don't have to
这就像一个已知的错误案例
这肯定会导致一个
long as it succeeds and we don't have to
worry about the failure case because the
错误 所以 有趣的事情
这是等我们有一点点
worry about the failure case because the
code we're generating here isn't the
设计决定 如果我们做 什么
是为了匹配我们的表达
code we're generating here isn't the
code for that isn't the code that
知道会导致错误
运行时根据我们的定义
code for that isn't the code that
handles errors so we know since we know
优化我们应该怎样做，我们
我们有一个优化的定义
handles errors so we know since we know
that the results of greater then must be
周一给了我们应该怎么做
是的， 也许可以调用错误
that the results of greater then must be
a boolean we don't need this entire test
马上就马上马上吧
我们应该做这个时间概念
a boolean we don't need this entire test
bool chunk this part of inserting the
它在编译器中
会是，也许就像马上一样
bool chunk this part of inserting the
code for test pool and where we add it
尽可能正确
失败与坏的权利让我们给一个
code for test pool and where we add it
in the list here
优化 的编译器定义 说
虽然这个
in the list here
these don't need to be part of this
那是什么，所以我们的 定义
优化关键部分是有
these don't need to be part of this
match
同样的答案和效果是
哎呀，这是我们的关键部分
if we were just thinking about moving
优化定义就是我们
可能生成不同的指令
if we were just thinking about moving
the code over and implementing this
这可能会做些不同的事情
速度或内存使用方面但是
the code over and implementing this
match case over here now we're still
我们生成的程序应该有
同样的答案 和相同的效果 ，让
match case over here now we're still
gonna have to do some stuff that has to
我们有几个地方
我们 可能有答案和 未来 的影响
gonna have to do some stuff that has to
do with the if and the then and the else
在这里所以并在 特定 的 一个
我们可能有些有趣的地方
do with the if and the then and the else
and things like that to compile those
发生了，他们就像是强调了
现在就在这里，我们要走了
and things like that to compile those
sub expressions but we don't need to
这 比两个人的操作 更重要
表达式如果有 效果会 怎样
sub expressions but we don't need to
test pool you had suggested that we
如果它们有效果会怎么样？
程序员期待着什么
test pool you had suggested that we
could get rid of a branch case to was a
发生在那里我想让你思考
约 一分钟什么的例子
could get rid of a branch case to was a
suggestion from the middle what was the
一个程序这是一个 程序 的示例
这有更大的影响
suggestion from the middle what was the
branch case you're suggesting we could
位置谈论这个对我来说有什么用
我的意思是 说 什么的一个例子
branch case you're suggesting we could
get rid of if we implement greater than
程序有在那里我已经影响
将这两个下划线圈在附近
get rid of if we implement greater than
with branch oh so are you saying we like
更大的是 一个程序 的 例子
这 有影响 ，谈论这个
with branch oh so are you saying we like
inside the greater than operation there
一分钟
好的，所以这里是这里的一个
inside the greater than operation there
might be a branch in there and we can
我 是一个 更简单的例子
可以想到说明这个或在
might be a branch in there and we can
make that branch do the if thing instead
如果我们有一个，那么至少是最短的
程序是这样的
make that branch do the if thing instead
so maybe we could get clever with
我们是一个添加结果的程序
大于打印一些
so maybe we could get clever with
compiling the greater than at this sort
表达式现在这意味着如果
我们 运行了一个未经授权的编译器
compiling the greater than at this sort
of at the same time as the if right so
会打印一张打印件来比较它们
大于然后错误
of at the same time as the if right so
there'd be some opportunities there okay
再加上我认为 这就是 这个程序
如果我们在未经优化的情况下运行它会怎么做
there'd be some opportunities there okay
so maybe we could go deeper into
编译器如果我们的优化排序
拿出来或取出那个操作
so maybe we could go deeper into
exploring that option the the point I
或者我们会在一开始就失败了
切换到优化编译器和
exploring that option the the point I
had in mind when I put this up that's an
事情会有所不同
他们是 我们的计划， 如果我们 不运行
had in mind when I put this up that's an
interesting idea I didn't have that idea
刚刚在这里失败，如果我们跳过了
这样做是因为它是
interesting idea I didn't have that idea
in mind when I picked this example the
我们 只会看到 一个错误
不同的答案出来可能会看到一个
in mind when I picked this example the
main thing I had in mind when I picked
如果 曾经是一个错误，那就 回答
我们要坚持 这个定义
main thing I had in mind when I picked
this example is pointing out this bool
我正在争论的优化是一个
好主意我们 可能会跳过一些
this example is pointing out this bool
case that we can get rid of this boolean
在这里工作就像我们知道如果更大
我们应该最终得到答案
case that we can get rid of this boolean
check by virtue of the fact that we know
错误， 所以我们可以跳过
做实际的加，因为我们知道
check by virtue of the fact that we know
that if we're doing a greater in if in
这会 产生一个错误，但我们
不应该完全避免编译
that if we're doing a greater in if in
the conditional position it's gonna
这或将其变成编译错误
这可能是我们做出的设计决定
the conditional position it's gonna
produce a boolean so there's no need to
关于尝试和报告 的 语言
像这样的错误 ，现在说
produce a boolean so there's no need to
check there's no way that omitting this
语言被更改 并报告这些
编译器中的各种错误，但我们
check there's no way that omitting this
code could cause this program to have a
不应该改变优化器
该 程序的 程序 的行为
code could cause this program to have a
different answer or have an error when
用来打印出来的东西
优化它应该仍然打印相同
different answer or have an error when
there wasn't an error before etc it's
事情没关系 所以这个 整体想法
整体想法出现在我们的
there wasn't an error before etc it's
gonna have the same answers so that's
编译器作为这些详细模式
匹配并使用这些 信息
gonna have the same answers so that's
pretty interesting it means that we
详细的模式匹配， 以使更好
决定
pretty interesting it means that we
could write these more detailed match
它被称为指令选择和
有一种可视化的思考方式
could write these more detailed match
cases on some expressions in the current
关于它，所以如果我们采取我们的一个 if
从上面我们可以想到 的方案
cases on some expressions in the current
compilers we have this is particularly
程序正在编写，我们已经 完成了
你可以考虑这个
compilers we have this is particularly
useful in expressions that do these tag
一种类似于递归的数据结构
就像我们的抽象语法树 和我们一样
useful in expressions that do these tag
checks for errors but there's other
通常不会这样画它们
类，但它是 有用 的绘制它
checks for errors but there's other
cases where this can be useful as well
方式有时让我们想象一下
如果 表达式是树，则 绘制此图
cases where this can be useful as well
we can write these more detailed match
所以我们匹配的ifs
细节有一个if在根然后 a
we can write these more detailed match
cases and do a better job of selecting
大于这 比 符号 少
然后比这边更大，
cases and do a better job of selecting
which instructions we generate for a
然后有两个表达式并在
Noah 是一个别的表达 和E 1
which instructions we generate for a
given expression so this site this idea
和E 2， 然后我们可以想到的其他
因为那些是完整的子树
given expression so this site this idea
has a name I'm just gonna write it over
可能是整个子表达式所以
如果匹配则整体if匹配
has a name I'm just gonna write it over
here this idea is called well it's
与我们的任何可能表达相匹配
可以把 它 想象 成 只是处理
here this idea is called well it's
really--it's there's a huge family of
树的这个节点然后它
处理一切这 整个左
really--it's there's a huge family of
techniques here but the overall idea is
手侧子树和 这两个子
树木分开 然后这些分开
techniques here but the overall idea is
called instruction selection and this is
子树会被其他树分解
自然 ，这是我们的
called instruction selection and this is
getting at this idea that right now
编译器现在每次 我们 做
看着这棵树我们来看看 在 一个节点
getting at this idea that right now
we've written sort of one case for each
树弄清楚如何处理做
一个节点， 然后递归处理所有
we've written sort of one case for each
expression in in our language right EF
子树更好有一些
表达我们更详细的匹配
expression in in our language right EF
has one case that matches it in the
正在挑选一大块树
处理更大块的时间
has one case that matches it in the
compiler EBU bully num e app everything
那个树一次处理和你
能想到我上面所做的一切
compiler EBU bully num e app everything
has one case that matches it in the
这个匹配的加法表达式
加上表达是不同的部分
has one case that matches it in the
compiler and there's only one option for
从根开始的表达式
是匹配的 ，然后是递归的
compiler and there's only one option for
which instructions we generate for each
最终得到了处理
递归调用所以其中一 件事
which instructions we generate for each
expression we generate it and the idea
你会在关于教学的文献中看到
选择， 我不会进去
expression we generate it and the idea
of instruction selection is well if we
深入到这一点，我想指出 ，以
你这个存在，但我们有有限
of instruction selection is well if we
use more information about what's going
时间131 1 这张照片得到了这个
在教学选择中的想法是 什么
use more information about what's going
on around an expression we can do some
我们正在做，我将继续前进
这个例子下来所以我可以得到这个
on around an expression we can do some
smarter things when we generate code
这幅画旁边的照片是我们的
当 我们选择指令 时， 我们 正在做
smarter things when we generate code
omitting omitting checks like this is
有一些代表我们的树
计划，我们已经得到了所有的 这些
omitting omitting checks like this is
one idea so I want to talk about this
不同的方式 ，我只是去
将它们作为这些抽象形状绘制出来
one idea so I want to talk about this
more generally but before I talk about
在一边编译节点的子集
在树中 进入有用的组装
more generally but before I talk about
it more generally I want to put a few
指令进入有用的目标机器
说明和我们的编译器是什么
it more generally I want to put a few
examples up here so another set of
试图用一种方式来查看我们的
编译器的作业是要 找到一个完整的
examples up here so another set of
examples here these are nested matches
覆盖这棵树的平铺
我们知道 如何编译的 不同方式
examples here these are nested matches
on on plus and they need some letters
注意所以可能有一个平铺
涉及用这种颜色抓住这些
on on plus and they need some letters
and the question I want to ask is which
抓住这些颜色 抓住 这些
用这种颜色然后这些
and the question I want to ask is which
of these
在这里，这可能是一种可能的方式
考虑整理这整棵树
which of these won't let us skip a tag
通过我们知道的方式将节点转换为
说明，如果你眯着眼睛看我们的
which of these won't let us skip a tag
check right so we just saw how if we
您可以想象的模式匹配
这里的紫色区域和 红色
check right so we just saw how if we
know that the thing in conditional
这里我们的嵌套匹配区域
匹配更多信息， 然后
know that the thing in conditional
position in an if is a greater than we
最底层的叶子节点就是东西
就像我们刚才的数字和布尔一样
position in an if is a greater than we
can skip the tag check for boolean's in
直接编译和 策略
我们在编译器中实现了一个
can skip the tag check for boolean's in
it what about this so these here's four
从开始贪婪策略
我们的编译器根本就是贪婪的
it what about this so these here's four
options of nested nested binary
匹配从根开始的东西
挑选可以找到的东西
options of nested nested binary
operators
根和重复的碎片和
如果有一整套文学作品
operators
well this let us do this should say well
如果你像毕业生一样思考的话
当然在编译器中或深入研究
well this let us do this should say well
this should say EEPROM to sorry about
编译器优化有一个完整的
关于思维方式的文献体
this should say EEPROM to sorry about
that just for consistency that way
这是一个平铺问题
表达你所 知道 的不同方式
five four three two one
如何编译节点的子集和
试图拿出 一个最佳的平铺
five four three two one
okay there's sort of a weirdness in one
这棵树，这是一个有趣的
合理地向前推进的方法
okay there's sort of a weirdness in one
of these options so I want you to talk
实现这一点的直截了当的方式
这也 与GCC的 做法 有关
of these options so I want you to talk
about it just for 20 or 30 seconds just
这是一堆手写的
这从根开始贪婪的规则和
about it just for 20 or 30 seconds just
talk about it briefly
走下去， 这真的是我们的模式
匹配在编译函数和
okay so what's so first of all what's
这就是GCC为一个体面的大块做的事情
它的指令选择等我
okay so what's so first of all what's
the what's the answer here or at least
只是想把这张照片 放在 这里
告诉你， 有这个东西
the what's the answer here or at least
like the the most obvious answer here
我们正在 做的是一个实现
战略 ，有一个整体
like the the most obvious answer here
well in B and C we're doing a plus and
你可以在编译器中完成研究生课程
谈谈这个人写的
well in B and C we're doing a plus and
then we know that the first argument is
关于如何做聪明的论文
指导选择，但我们是我们
then we know that the first argument is
either a number or another plus and we
这种贪婪可以走得很远
策略从根使用 的 起始
either a number or another plus and we
know that numbers well numbers don't
更多信息
这样的指令选择和
know that numbers well numbers don't
need to be checked for being numbers and
这是我们可以 采取我们可以看到的一种方式
从我们现有的编译器和实现
need to be checked for being numbers and
we know that plus plus expressions have
它自己如何做一点点
更好地生成汇编代码
we know that plus plus expressions have
to return numbers so in B and C we can
关于这个想法的问题
高层次的 想法
to return numbers so in B and C we can
definitely omit the tag check for the
好吧所以一个好， 所以我要忍受
一些汇编代码
definitely omit the tag check for the
first argument we don't have to check
我只是想强调我实际上只是
我想突出其中的一部分
first argument we don't have to check
the tag of this expression or this
想要它，因为我想通过
今天所有这三个想法都非常 值得强调
the tag of this expression or this
expression we can just skip it and maybe
只是一个小片 我 的意思是这
类似于 我所拥有 的 代码
expression we can just skip it and maybe
even generate even more intelligent
周一我要 强调的是
就在这里，这是你的代码
even generate even more intelligent
instructions there in the first case in
可能已经在生成的 代码中 看到了
您的编译器 很多， 但模式
instructions there in the first case in
answer a like if we have a function
一遍 又一 遍地 出现
在我们的编译器的生成代码中
answer a like if we have a function
application we don't know that much
我们采取斧头中的值来移动它
到堆栈 然后我们采取
application we don't know that much
locally to this pattern match about what
在 这个堆栈地址值并将其移动
回到EAX 并且非常高兴
locally to this pattern match about what
could possibly be returned from that
在那个额外的工作，所以 有一个
非常直率的直截了当
could possibly be returned from that
function the way we have our compiler
方法来处理这种
这是 关于编译输出的问题
function the way we have our compiler
set up we don't know much at all about
因为我不知道 它是否值得
称它为蛮力， 但它就像
set up we don't know much at all about
the return values of functions until we
这是一个 聪明 的解决方案
只有它的简单才是这样的一种方式
the return values of functions until we
call them so option A it's really hard
谈谈让这更好地避免
这种情况和编译输出是让我们的
call them so option A it's really hard
to see how we would skip a check check
想象写一个叫做的函数
提高接受一个指令
to see how we would skip a check check
by using option a we kind of have to do
指令清单，它会去
产生一个新的指令列表就这样了
by using option a we kind of have to do
the function call see what comes back
只是做出指示
更好，这个想法就是这样
the function call see what comes back
and then do the addition with it so the
提高说明会去的
打印出来之前的编译器
and then do the addition with it so the
most obvious answer here is a and it's
说明正确，我们如何做
编译器工作我们解析我们编译到
most obvious answer here is a and it's
sort of the intended answer but D is
得到一个指令清单，然后我们
打印出所有说明吧
sort of the intended answer but D is
intentionally weird B is intentionally
这是最后一步， 让我们想象一下
之前改进了教学清单
intentionally weird B is intentionally
weird what's weird about D that's weird
将它打印出来让它成为一个
更好的教学清单，这是一种方法
weird what's weird about D that's weird
about D yeah yeah yeah a one is
这就是这 几乎是一个
很多我告诉你的 是
about D yeah yeah yeah a one is
definitely gonna produce a boolean which
简单的一件事是在实践中完成 ，
工作让我们的指令匹配
definitely gonna produce a boolean which
means the plus expression is definitely
与和说明，让我们想象一下，
在指令列表中，我们 的前方
means the plus expression is definitely
going to cause an error when it runs
有一个reg偏移的眼睛移动
EBP 和一些数字N 和Reg ya X.
going to cause an error when it runs
right this is like a known error case
然后是注册斧头和a的眼睛移动
reg偏移相同的数字
right this is like a known error case
right it's definitely going to cause an
那里
让我在右边写这个
right it's definitely going to cause an
error so one interesting thing about
模式棘轮风格好吧这样
与此事相关联的事情
error so one interesting thing about
this is wait we have a little bit of a
其余的说明如果
我们到堆栈移动和 EAX
this is wait we have a little bit of a
design decision about what to do if we
然后我们将价值从中移开
堆叠回EAX 我们知道哪个
design decision about what to do if we
were to match on an expression that we
指令是冗余的，其
指令是第一个冗余
were to match on an expression that we
know is going to cause an error at
第二条指令的说明
第二个权利我们要把它 移到
know is going to cause an error at
runtime according to our definition of
堆栈 ，因为我们可以看看它
后来我们 绝对不需要 移动
runtime according to our definition of
an optimization what should we do we
它从堆栈中退回到EAX中
现在我们可以采取这个，然后转身
an optimization what should we do we
have a definition of an optimization we
这是第一条指令
我用Reg移动第一个
have a definition of an optimization we
gave on Monday what should we do
一
链接到休息说明链接
gave on Monday what should we do
yeah maybe make maybe call an error
intereste 回答 所以只是放下第二个
指令列表中的指令
yeah maybe make maybe call an error
right away oh right away right away
在打印之前应该调整一下
使其更有用，如 一个调整
right away oh right away right away
there's this notion of time should we do
在这里我可以做到这一点
更有用的是 呼叫提高
there's this notion of time should we do
it in the compiler
再说一遍，我可以
递归调用改进指令
would be and maybe as right away as
其余 只是休息所以
在这里， 我可以改进说明
would be and maybe as right away as
possible right as right away as possible
其余的指示是的，是的
去吧啊有趣 但所以为什么
possible right as right away as possible
is fail with bad right let's give a
为什么我没有说 什么
关于这些引导 指令如此
is fail with bad right let's give a
compiler definition of optimization say
正如我 所说 ，这里发生了什么
它正在 这个递归中出现
compiler definition of optimization say
about this though
打电话是我们说我们 要去的
从 前面处理说明
well what yeah so our definition of
如果我们得到指令的前缀
在这里，我们认识到我们可以做到
well what yeah so our definition of
optimization the key part was having the
我们会 更好地 将它们切掉
我们会把它们砍掉来回答 你的问题
optimization the key part was having the
same answer and effects that was the
问是的所以我们正在 谈论
这 是我现在的 递归电话
same answer and effects that was the
whoops that was the key part of our
那种说法 好吧好吧所以我们要去
然后对其余的进行 递归调用
whoops that was the key part of our
optimization definition was that we
这个问题就像我们一样
删除第一个指令是什么
optimization definition was that we
might generate different instructions
发生在第一个指令
对， 我们要谈谈
might generate different instructions
which might do something different in
这个功能有点 的结构
更多，所以我们肯定会再次发生
which might do something different in
terms of speed or memory usage but the
这样我们就可以循环其他什么呢
我们需要 担心 的是啊是啊
terms of speed or memory usage but the
program we generate ought to have the
所以我们可以打电话给改进
关于整件事的说明正确
program we generate ought to have the
same answer and the same effects so
因为我们可能已经嘎吱嘎吱
指令一起在前面 那个
same answer and the same effects so
we're so there's a couple places where
然后再做一个模式匹配我们
也可以改善我们的权利
we're so there's a couple places where
we might have answers and effects coming
这样做可能是另一个
这里的方法就是打电话来打电话
we might have answers and effects coming
out here so and in particular one of the
改善对这件事的指示
是的，让我们一定要做
out here so and in particular one of the
places we might have interesting things
当我们这样做时，列表会变小，所以我们
不必 担心它是一个
places we might have interesting things
happening and they're like underscored
无限循环， 因为 我们只要我们
最终使列表变小
happening and they're like underscored
out right now is right here we're going
我们会坐下来 一个 空的列表 或 一些
固定大小的列表， 但我们可以
out right now is right here we're going
to do this greater than operation on two
只是 在 整个事情 上 调用 它
也许这表明了一些新的模式
to do this greater than operation on two
expressions what if they have effects
这将 是真正的问题是什么
如果没有模式匹配，但 我认为是
expressions what if they have effects
what if they have effects what if the
我认为其实什么 是
你的问题正确，因为
what if they have effects what if the
programmer was expecting something to
如果我们这样做 ，我们会怎么做
只是这整个名单上的功能它
programmer was expecting something to
happen there what I want you to think
只会说好的 没有比赛没有比赛
工作正确你说它说移动EBP
happen there what I want you to think
about for a minute what's an example of
顶部的ESP 无关
你建议的比赛所以
about for a minute what's an example of
a program it's an example of a program
我们要做的事情是我们需要的，我们可能
有更多的情况我们知道如何
that has effects in this greater
改善这里的指示， 但我们
我们需要一些结局案例
that has effects in this greater
position talk about this for me what do
指令与其他部分相关联
说明和我们说 没事
position talk about this for me what do
I mean by that what is an example of a
没有任何匹配让我们向前迈进
列表，让我们把它 变成我
I mean by that what is an example of a
program that has effects where I've
联系以 改善指示骚乱
因为我们无法 做到
program that has effects where I've
circled these two underscores for near
如果它不匹配的话
任何我们可以工作 的 模式
circled these two underscores for near
greater what's an example of a program
所以这里的想法就是这样
我们将遍历整个 列表
greater what's an example of a program
that has effects there talk about this
说明 ，每次我们找到
我们知道怎么做的小前缀
that has effects there talk about this
for a minute
改善 我们会缩小那个然后
我们会看到，如果我们 可以做的更好 的
okay so here's here's one of the here's
还剩下什么，所以这是非常的
具体非常类似我 猜的直率
okay so here's here's one of the here's
sort of one of the simpler examples I
这是个好词， 有一个列表
说明 ，我们看到说明
sort of one of the simpler examples I
can think of to illustrate this or at
彼此相邻，我们可以改进
让我们改进 它们并把新的
can think of to illustrate this or at
least the shortest what if we have a
在地方和更好的说明
这里的想法是我们 运行一点点
least the shortest what if we have a
program like this
窗口我们可以把它想象成 一 点点
沿着序列的一个小窗口
we're a program that adds the result of
说明 ，这是一个小点
我们偷窥并尝试使用的地方
we're a program that adds the result of
greater than on printing some
非常非常本地化的信息
一个，两个或 三个或四个 指令
greater than on printing some
expressions now this would mean that if
时间让事情变得更好 一点点
这个想法 有一个名字peephole
expressions now this would mean that if
we ran on an unauthorized compiler this
优化，这是一个超级
普通它也相对一个不错
we ran on an unauthorized compiler this
would print one print to compare them
这个特点就是它没有
要求了解 其余部分
would print one print to compare them
for greater than and then error on the
编译器中的一些 知道嵌套
匹配需要了解很多
for greater than and then error on the
plus I thought it's what this program
关于每个表达式的假设
做什么以及它可能有什么错误
plus I thought it's what this program
would do if we ran it on the unoptimized
它可以拥有什么标签
通过了解x86是什么来实现
would do if we ran it on the unoptimized
compiler if our optimization sort of
应该做对你只需要
知道x86这样做 是因为你
compiler if our optimization sort of
took that out or took out that operation
只需要知道那 不可能
第二条指令不可能
took that out or took out that operation
or just failed in the beginning we would
有用， 因为它只是在做
不必要的工作，所以它是那种
or just failed in the beginning we would
switch to the optimizing compiler and
独立于编译器的其余部分
这很好，而且非常好
switch to the optimizing compiler and
things would just be way different than
只是循环遍历指令
看着 几个 旁边， 是 每个
things would just be way different than
they were our program wouldn't run if we
其他 一次是的
所以，让我们记住让我们留下来
they were our program wouldn't run if we
just failed with here and if we skipped
请注意，你的评论 是 正确的
也许我们可以完成 整个过程
just failed with here and if we skipped
doing this operation because it was
列表 ，我们没有找到任何说明
改进，但我想指出
doing this operation because it was
known to be an error we would just see
花在那里的 时间不是编译时间
运行时间正确，这很漂亮
known to be an error we would just see
different answers come out might see an
这实际上是一个重要的区别
在所有这些权利中，这些
different answers come out might see an
answer when it used to be an error so if
匹配更多的优化
一些喜欢平铺或做的东西
answer when it used to be an error so if
we're going to uphold this definition of
这种人优化都是成本
编译时间， 我们正在交易
we're going to uphold this definition of
an optimization which I'm arguing is a
努力， 以便最终的计划
我经常给出的例子运行得更快
an optimization which I'm arguing is a
good idea we might be able to skip some
因为如果你是你知道的话
适合Firefox的项目经理
good idea we might be able to skip some
work here like we know that if greater
你会，你应该能够并且 应该
如果你是 某人的权衡
work here like we know that if greater
produces an answer we should eventually
给你一个优化编译器
花了一个星期的时间 来运行但是让Firefox如此
produces an answer we should eventually
error right so we might be able to skip
你可以并且应该雇用服务器
编译Firefox一周然后
error right so we might be able to skip
doing the actual plus because we know
二进制一次发布的那个
为您的数百万用户提供更快的权利
doing the actual plus because we know
this is going to produce an error but we
所以这是你的 问题 非常好
因为它 正是如此
this is going to produce an error but we
shouldn't completely avoid compiling
权衡权利Mozilla应该感到高兴
运行最好的窥视孔优化器
shouldn't completely avoid compiling
this or turn it into a compile error
在这个世界上，如果能节省我一天的话
第二个权利，因为我是数百万之一
this or turn it into a compile error
that might be a design decision we make
用户可以， 所以让我们看到最后
我想谈谈的 想法
that might be a design decision we make
about the language to try and report
今天是我想的 几个
房间的不同区域 长大了
about the language to try and report
errors like this and say now the
周一 我们刚刚说话的时候
有点头脑风暴的改进方法
errors like this and say now the
language is changed and reports these
改进编译器并且有
事情就像这样， 这是
language is changed and reports these
kinds of errors in the compiler but we
在例子中出现的东西
我是在课堂上画的第一个
kinds of errors in the compiler but we
should not have the optimizer changing
我们写的程序就是这样的
这就像第二周 或者回来的那样
should not have the optimizer changing
the behavior of the program the program
三 ，你们 很多 人都像乔一样
我知道这就产生了 八个原因
the behavior of the program the program
used to print something out when it's
编译二进制权，就像那样
你没有在那里取得多少成就
used to print something out when it's
optimized it should still print the same
编译该程序然后运行
并有两个观察使
optimized it should still print the same
thing okay so this overall idea this
关于这个程序， 一个就是那个
在这里它是一个表达式
thing okay so this overall idea this
overall idea which shows up in our
添加两个常数，然后是
另一个稍微微妙的事情
overall idea which shows up in our
compiler as these detailed pattern
在这里 这是一个使用
变量，我们知道它的价值，而我
compiler as these detailed pattern
matches and using information from these
把知识放在引号中因为我们是
人们对此做了很多推理
matches and using information from these
detailed pattern matches to make better
确保我们理解 我们是
添加三分之一，这是不会做的
detailed pattern matches to make better
decisions
任何像溢出的权利，但X是
一些变量，我们知道它的价值
decisions
it's called instruction selection and
将是四个，没有办法
当我们运行它时，值不会是4
it's called instruction selection and
there's sort of a visual way to think
程序所以有两个不同的 东西
继续我们在那里使用
there's sort of a visual way to think
about it so if we take one of our if
聪明人才知道 这一点
程序 将 产生这个答案
about it so if we take one of our if
programs from above we can think of the
实际上有时会发生一件事
在第一对编程中
programs were writing and we've done
本课程的作业是人
写的 是复杂的编译器
programs were writing and we've done
this you can think about this for any
他们这样做是因为他们
可能实现了一个翻译
this you can think about this for any
kind of recursive data structure like
CS c130 如果他们编译了这个
程序让我们只调用这个 程序P.
kind of recursive data structure like
like our abstract syntax trees and we
目前
我们编译了P类的意义
like our abstract syntax trees and we
don't usually draw them this way in this
什么是我们可以做的最好的编译
这个程序很好，如果我们这样会很好
don't usually draw them this way in this
class but it's useful to draw them this
可以将此程序编译为 移动 EA
x17对，因为 那是
class but it's useful to draw them this
way sometimes so let's just a imagine
的八表示，这将是
很酷， 如果我们编译这个程序的话
way sometimes so let's just a imagine
drawing this if expression out is a tree
只是把 答案变成了答案
EAX 还有 竟是 几个你
drawing this if expression out is a tree
so the ifs that we were matching on in
谁做了这样的事我很善良
它实际上有点 放慢你的速度
so the ifs that we were matching on in
detail had an if at the root then a
当你需要解析一个处理时
输入，因为你无法处理所有
detail had an if at the root then a
greater than a that's a less than sign
可能即将来临的未知价值
进入一个程序， 但对于 一个程序
greater than a that's a less than sign
and then a greater than on this side and
我们实际可以写的所有已知值
进入我们的编译器就足够聪明了
and then a greater than on this side and
then there were two expressions and in
它可以弄清楚这些常数是什么
应该并生成更好的代码
then there were two expressions and in
Noah's of an an else expression and E 1
对于其中一些案例和我们的一种方式
能做到这一点 是 我们能做到的
Noah's of an an else expression and E 1
and E 2 and then an else we can think of
这基于 我们迄今为止所知道的方式
可以这么说，也许是绿色的东西
and E 2 and then an else we can think of
as being full sub trees because those
基于我们目前所知的+1 3
是啊
as being full sub trees because those
could be whole sub expressions so the
对，所以一个想法是一个好主意
想做 选择权的 想法
could be whole sub expressions so the
the overall if match right the if match
我们可以说 用一个 来表达+
Eden嗯和enum这是一个特殊的
the overall if match right the if match
that matched any possible expression we
编译权可能 只是添加
将这 两个数字放在一起 并编译成
that matched any possible expression we
could think of that as just handling
一个单一的移动指令就是一个
想法但它对 我们 没有帮助
could think of that as just handling
this node of the tree and then it
这个X变量的其他问题是哪个
价值我们知道这些事情之一
this node of the tree and then it
handled everything else this entire left
好像它可能是一个指令
选择这样的事情， 但 其他
handled everything else this entire left
hand side sub tree and these two sub
一个看起来不像是一个
指令选择的东西
hand side sub tree and these two sub
trees separately and then these separate
特别是如果那个X使用那个X.
有点远离它的位置
trees separately and then these separate
sub trees would get broken up by other
定义但这些是相关的想法
因为他们都与价值观有关
sub trees would get broken up by other
naturals that's sort of what our
我们 我们知道当我们编译
程序必须 是我们特定的价值
naturals that's sort of what our
compilers are doing now every time we
不需要等待并运行程序
搞清楚它们是什么值，因此
compilers are doing now every time we
look at this tree we look at one node in
这里有一个我们可以 使用的想法
而不是写而不是写
look at this tree we look at one node in
the tree figure out what to do with that
使这部分编译功能
并本着 我们刚刚所做 的精神
the tree figure out what to do with that
one node and then recursively handle all
对于人们的 优化让我们想象一下
函数调用提高表达式
one node and then recursively handle all
the sub trees better there is some
采取表达并产生一个
表达式 ， 更好是
the sub trees better there is some
expressions our more detailed match
较短或较少的子
表达式或以某种方式减少工作量
is picking a larger chunk of the tree at
让我们想象一下，我们可以写出来
改善表达
is picking a larger chunk of the tree at
a time to handle picking a larger chunk
这里的第一个案例是 你
建议那就像
a time to handle picking a larger chunk
of the tree at a time to handle and you
指令选择版本
如果我们想要的话，这是正确的
of the tree at a time to handle and you
can think of everything I did above with
改进有优势的EEPROM 工具
第一个位置然后是eID麻木
can think of everything I did above with
the plus expression this matching on the
和1和E 麻木 - 什么是 更好
这个表达式内存的版本应该
the plus expression this matching on the
plus expression to be different parts of
有一个更好的类型表达式
这个表达式 的 版本 更好
plus expression to be different parts of
the expression starting at the root that
使用的表达式比这个
我们想要一种更快捷的方式
the expression starting at the root that
are matched and then recursive pieces
同样的结果是的，所以一个建议
用一些 进入EAX + 1 + + 2
are matched and then recursive pieces
end up getting handled by doing
字符串字符串填写什么问题
与这又会有什么问题
end up getting handled by doing
recursive calls so one of the things
它不是一个坏主意，这有点 的
与指令选择相同的想法
recursive calls so one of the things
you'll see in literature on instruction
想法是啊是啊也许有一些
转向做它是啊
you'll see in literature on instruction
selection and I'm going to not go too in
溢出还有其他什么东西
还有更多的东西
selection and I'm going to not go too in
depth into this I want to point out to
关于我如何决定写这个
改善表达功能我应该
depth into this I want to point out to
you that this exists but we have finite
打扰你，是的，是的，我们
只是想要返回一个表达式
you that this exists but we have finite
time in 131 1 this picture gets at this
如果我们开始把它变成
说明就像是一个
time in 131 1 this picture gets at this
idea in instruction selection that what
没有骆驼级别的类型错误，所以我得到了
这个想法与这个想法不同
idea in instruction selection that what
we are doing and I'm going to just move
根据这个选择说明
想要一个我想要的东西
we are doing and I'm going to just move
this example down so I can get this
类型表达式是+ 1 + +的枚举
那是非常有趣的
this example down so I can get this
picture next to this picture what we are
非常有趣 我可以参加
表达，你知道我们会做一些
picture next to this picture what we are
doing when we select instructions is we
我们会做通常的递归事情
表达所以我们会找到任何子
doing when we select instructions is we
have some tree that represents our
其他匹配案例中的表达式
但如果我们找到的东西 ，这是一个
have some tree that represents our
program and we've got all of these
原始的，它是 两个加号
数字， 我们可以取代它
program and we've got all of these
different ways and I'm just going to
表达式的数字是
另外的那 两个东西 ，你只是
different ways and I'm just going to
draw them as these abstract shapes off
替换 它
我们不得不担心一些
draw them as these abstract shapes off
to the side to compile subsets of nodes
溢出，我们可能需要 把它变成
表达式 抛出的东西
to the side to compile subsets of nodes
in the tree into useful assembly
溢出错误， 如果它们溢出 但是
如果他们不溢出这 是
in the tree into useful assembly
instructions into useful target machine
肯定会产生 相同的
回答这很有意思
instructions into useful target machine
instructions and what our compiler is
非常有趣的有啥这个
另一个案例我们谈过这个案子
instructions and what our compiler is
trying to do one way to view what our
我将要 做到这一点
稍微简单的情况只是为了我要去
trying to do one way to view what our
compilers job is is to find a complete
想象一下，有一个数字
不是没有一些复合表达
compilers job is is to find a complete
covering tiling of this tree with
但左边的数字让绑定
我们如何改善这一点
covering tiling of this tree with
different ways we know how to compile
表达我们怎样才能 改善这一点
表达我们知道有一个数字
different ways we know how to compile
notes so there might be one tiling that
有没有 X，我们可以做，使该
更好
notes so there might be one tiling that
involves grabbing these with this color
是啊
所以建议是，我们必须
involves grabbing these with this color
grabbing these with this color grabbing
想到类型是有意义的让我们
想象一下，我们有一些 你想要的 帮手
grabbing these with this color grabbing
these with this color and then these
用枚举替换X的所有实例
的 在主体N， 其中替换将要
these with this color and then these
down here that might be one possible way
必须是我们的其他一些辅助功能
对
down here that might be one possible way
to think about tiling this entire tree
那很有意思
因此这表明 ， 也许我们有这个
to think about tiling this entire tree
with ways we know to turn nodes into
我们可以做的其他改造
表达式，如果我们知道a
with ways we know to turn nodes into
instructions and if you squint at our
特定的标识符总是如此
被绑定到我们可以相同的价值
instructions and if you squint at our
pattern matches you could imagine that
到处替换它的 价值
我们不再需要那个了
pattern matches you could imagine that
the the purple region here and the red
变量 在 咱们的工作是
有价值的地方生活
the the purple region here and the red
region here our nested matches where we
在我们评估之后我们可以看一下
它多次，但 如果我们知道什么
region here our nested matches where we
matched on more information and then
这 是没有理由 去的
存储它并查找多个
matched on more information and then
the bottom most leaf nodes are things
当我们得到时 ，我们只是使用那个值
如果我们可以取代所有的
the bottom most leaf nodes are things
like numbers and boolean's that we just
Eid X在体内的实例
然后 我们得到 那个 数字表达式
like numbers and boolean's that we just
compile very directly and the strategy
节省 查找 该变量的时间
每次遇到它我们永远不会
compile very directly and the strategy
we have implemented in our compiler is a
必须将变量存储在第一个中
地点
we have implemented in our compiler is a
greedy strategy that starts from the
所以只是给出这些的定义
事我想我会谈 一 点点
greedy strategy that starts from the
root what our compiler does is greedily
这个案子 周五 更多关于他们
所谓主要所以如果你想看看
root what our compiler does is greedily
matches things starting from the root
他们这种情况称为常数
传播你采取常数和移动
matches things starting from the root
picking picking what it can find from
他们到了